<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Parkrun on Stoyan&#39;s notes</title>
    <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/tags/parkrun/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Parkrun on Stoyan&#39;s notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 08:00:00 +0930</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sshopov.github.io/notes/tags/parkrun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkun 175 - R2D2 drops in</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun175-starwars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun175-starwars/</guid>
      <description>For parkrun 175 Hugo built an R2D2 look-a-like Lego Mindstorms robot and I programmed it to help deliver the speech. Here is how it went:
Me: [madly pulling out the battery to do a hard reset after the program didn&amp;rsquo;t want to exit from the morning&amp;rsquo;s test run]  Hard rest R2D2   Me: Welcome I found this droid on the way to parkrun and it says it has an urgent message for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkrun 167 - Cheers</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun167-cheers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 23:51:01 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun167-cheers/</guid>
      <description>Good morning and welcome! Welcome to parkrun 167!
There was a TV show called Cheers when I was growing up. I was little and didn&amp;rsquo;t get it, but the title song stuck with me. The two lines I remember the most from it are:
Where everybody knows your name And they&amp;rsquo;re always glad you came
These two lines popped into my head recently and I thought this is just like parkrun: I know everyone&amp;rsquo;s name because I process the results and everyone is glad I came because I bring the stopwatch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkrun 162 - April Fools&#39; Day</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun162-april_fools_day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun162-april_fools_day/</guid>
      <description>Good morning and welcome to parkrun (what number are we up to?)!
I am feeling a bit lazy this morning, so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d be a director instead of a runner. So lazy in fact, that I thought I&amp;rsquo;d oursource as many responsibilities as possible.
Please raise your hand if you are a regular parkrunner? Please raise your hand if you are a first timer or a visitor? Welcome! Regular parkrunners, can you please adopt a first timer or a visitor after the speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkrun 157 - pre-flight safety briefing</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun157-flight_safety_briefing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun157-flight_safety_briefing/</guid>
      <description>Welcome aboard parkrun flight 157. I am your captain Stoyan and our lovely cabin crew is Sharon, Jonathan, Kiora, Jordan, Joy, Karen [cabin crew please line up and wave when your name is called]. You too can join our crew, simply sign up when you scan your barcode at the end.
Today we are travelling to there and back at altitude of 360m and your flight time depends on how much you are willing to suffer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkrun 151 - Thalia</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun151-thalia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun151-thalia/</guid>
      <description>Good morning and welcome to parkrun 151, which also happens to be the total number of Pokémon in the original set.
It seems to be a bit cold this morning so let&amp;rsquo;s warm up with a bit of clapping.
Rub hands, ok, ready?
Let&amp;rsquo;s hear it for our volunteers Aimee on stopwatch, Jasmin &amp;amp; Andrew on finish tokens, Julie &amp;amp; Rebekah behind the scanner, Jonathan bringing up the rear and Lucy behind the camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkun 145 - Hugo&#39;s 10th run and mantras to run with</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun145-mantras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun145-mantras/</guid>
      <description>145 CXLV 12^2 + 1^2 = 8^2 + 9^2 = 1!+4!+5! factorion
Welcome to parkrun 1 4 5, which also happens to be the title of a Cat Empire song.
Let&amp;rsquo;s see if we have any first timers. What about visitors from another parkrun? We run this way past our beautiful wetlands. Don&amp;rsquo;t get distracted by the abundant birdlife or you might miss the turn around sign near Bald Hills Rd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkun 139 - Leslie&#39;s 100th</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun139-leslie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun139-leslie/</guid>
      <description>19 + 23 + 29 + 31 + 37 = 139 all prime numbers 34th prime CXXXIX 100010112
Good morning and welcome to parkrun 139 or as my 3-year old daughter calls it &amp;ldquo;the party&amp;rdquo;.
I would like to acknowledge that today we&amp;rsquo;ll be running on the land of the Peramagk people.
I would also like to acknowledge all of our volunteers. We have a very experienced crew today. We are in the very safe hands of David on stopwatch, Jordan on finish tokens, the Bracken family Cameron, Andrew and Declan on token scanning and sorting, the cousins Gary and Paul are our photographer and marshal (and welcome back to you both).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkun 135 - Simon&#39;s 50th</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun135-simon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun135-simon/</guid>
      <description>5im0n 135 = (1+3+5)x(1*3*5) = 1^1+3^2+5^3 = 11*n^2 + 11*n + 3 for n=3
Good morning and welcome to Mount Barker parkrun 135. A lucky number with rare mathematical properties and you can read more about it on the pavement over there.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to start with an apology today. Last time I was in charge I said &amp;ldquo;Run this way until you see a flag near Bald Hills Rd, turn around it and come back&amp;rdquo; and then it turned out that there was no half-way flag; some people never turned around and for all I know may still be running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkun 130 - volunteers rule</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun130-volunteers_rule/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun130-volunteers_rule/</guid>
      <description>Good morning and welcome to Mount Barker parkrun CXXX, which is the Roman numeral for 130.
Are there any first timers? Welcome. What about visitors? Where are you from? Run this way until you see a flag near Bald Hills Rd, turn around it and come back.
Quick quiz: what do you get when you mix the Indian spring festival of Color Holi with a 5km race and charity fundraiser. The answer is the Color run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkun 106 - song threat</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun106-song_threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun106-song_threat/</guid>
      <description>Laaaa [warming up the vocal chords]
Top of the parkrun morning to you friends!
Ah it&amp;rsquo;s so good to be here again. I get so excited about parkrun that I wrote a song about it. Grette is going to help me with it. The song is about a runner who gets lost in a crowd and it goes something like this&amp;hellip;
Before I start are there any first timers today? And what about visitors from another parkrun?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkun 121 - election day</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun121-election_day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun121-election_day/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to parkrun 121!
Today is election day. Today you choose between progress and stagnation. Today you choose between weak and strong. Today you choose between health and sickness. Today you vote with your feet. I&amp;rsquo;d like to congratulate you all for choosing progress, strength and health by being here with us this morning.
Are there any first time voters? How about visiting voters?
Today we celebrate 100 parkruns for one of our regular voters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkun 127 - late night</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun127-late_night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun127-late_night/</guid>
      <description>True story: I went to a work dinner last night. Got employee of the year award. That wasn&amp;rsquo;t hard. I was the only one who hang around for the whole year. It was so loud there though that I lost my voice talking to people. Then I came back so late I had no time to prepare my speech for this morning. So I thought I just confess up front that I&amp;rsquo;ll be mostly improvising today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkun 117 - once upon a time</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun117-once_upon_a_time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2016 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun117-once_upon_a_time/</guid>
      <description>Hi, welcome I have a little story for you this morning.
Once upon a time there was a little boy.
His favourite day of the week was Saturday because he got to get up early and go to parkrun with his neighbour.
The boy loved parkrun. He loved looking at the crowd of friendly faces and listening to the run director&amp;rsquo;s welcome speech.
That day
13 June Queen&amp;rsquo;s Birthday fun run where you run 5km without a watch and whoever gets the closest to their estimated time wins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkun 111 - our inaugural fashion parade</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun111-fashion_parade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun111-fashion_parade/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the inaugural 2016 parkrun fashion parade. We have a lot of exceptional models lined up for you so let&amp;rsquo;s get started.
First up we have Kent who wears his signature smile and a PB of 18:45. He is only the second home grown parkrunner after Errol to hit the 100 mark. Kent has been a parkrun tourist at more venues than I have had hot meals. He is a regular pacer and one of our fastest and most accomplished runners, but this is not his biggest achievement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkun 101 - wedding speech</title>
      <link>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun101-wedding_speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 08:00:00 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sshopov.github.io/notes/post/parkrun101-wedding_speech/</guid>
      <description>Dearly beloved, we are gathered here today to run our Saturday parkrun. Not to be entered into lightly, parkrun should be entered into solemnly and with reverence and honour, a proper warmup and half-decent footwear. Into this holy agreement we come together to get healthier and stronger so we may serve others.
If there are any first timers please raise your hand or miss out for you only get one chance to be a first timer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>